Guide to Tuli Kupferberg and Sylvia Topp Papers MSS.385
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. Cartoons/Collages, 1964, 1970-2008, undated; 20 Linear Feet in .5 record carton, 44 manuscript boxes, 1 flat folder, 3 oversize flat folders, 1 flat-file folder
  - Photo Ed for War, 1993 (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - Mrs. Ben -- Lux, 1993 (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - Vietnam War in Color, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 113, Folder 23)
  - Bogart / Deadline USA. The Fighting Editor, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 113, Folder 24)
  - Every Little Meaning, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 25)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- No Daily Paper, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 26)
  - Openers, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 27)
  - I'd Hate It, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 113, Folder 28)
  - Manuals, 1985 (Box 113, Folder 29)
  - Killer Clinton and Layla, 1993 (Box 113, Folder 30)
  - HIstory Will Show Our Stupidity, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 113, Folder 31)
  - Union Beer, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 113, Folder 32)
  - JP Morgan Ass, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 33)
  - Get the Code Book, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 113, Folder 34)
  - Anti-Heros Series, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 113, Folder 35)
  - PIM, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 113, Folder 36)
  - Twinky, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 113, Folder 37)
  - Nutritional, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 113, Folder 38)
  - Art and Artists, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 113, Folder 39)
  - Jesse, 1980, 1995 (Box 113, Folder 40)
  - Mine is Proper, Yours is Grander, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 113, Folder 41)
  - Interior, circa 1984 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Start WW3, 1986 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Sons of Bitches, 1986 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Zaccaro, 1986 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Ron's Fav Joke, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Anything You Say, Howard, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Ferraro, 1985 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Ron's Imagine, 1985 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Reagan Eyes, 1985 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Each Paper / The Next, 1994 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Reagan -- Sting, 1986 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - America Doesn't Learn, 1986 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - I Forgot, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Hart, circa 1987 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - The President Lost It, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Ronald Reagan's Band, 1986 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - I'm Not a President, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - Crime Stoppers, 1988 (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - Hood Reagan, 1988 (Box 114, Folder 19)
  - Madame Lazonga, 1988 (Box 114, Folder 20)
  - Great Moments in Rock and Roll, circa 1980s (Box 114, Folder 21)
  - Could Use a Few Good Sticks, undated (Box 114, Folder 22)
  - Jewish American (Ex)Perience, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - Czar -- Vodka, 1980, 1982 (Box 114, Folder 24)
  - Post No Bills, circa 1980-1999 (Box 114, Folder 25)
  - Prezcam, circa 1980-1999 (Box 114, Folder 26)
  - Melancholy Baby, circa 1980-1999 (Box 114, Folder 27)
  - Assertiveness -- Fuck Off, circa 1980-1999 (Box 114, Folder 28)
  - Giuliani, 1986-2006 (Box 114, Folder 29-30)
  - Break for People, 1981 (Box 114, Folder 31)
  - Self-Portrait, 2000 (Box 114, Folder 32)
  - Takeh a Fascist, 2000 (Box 114, Folder 33)
  - Salute Our Vets, circa 2000-2010 (Box 114, Folder 34)
  - God the Faminist: She Don't Dig / Like Bras, 1999 (Box 114, Folder 35)
  - Death Circ, 1999 (Box 114, Folder 36)
  - For Art Youngs 50 Yr Old Cart on Same Subject, 2000 (Box 114, Folder 37)
  - Homeless Poetry, 1985-1990 (Box 114, Folder 38)
  - Tompkins Square, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 39)
  - Just Go Fuck Myself, circa 1984-2002 (Box 114, Folder 40)
  - Ta Beggars, circa 1984-2002 (Box 114, Folder 41)
  - Park Closed, 1984-2000 (Box 114, Folder 42)
  - Years Wasted on Les, circa 1984-2002 (Box 114, Folder 43)
  - A and P Art and Politics, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 44)
  - Wasted on Les, circa 1984-2002 (Box 114, Folder 45)
  - Koch and Graffiti Dogs, 1981-1986 (Box 114, Folder 46)
  - Koch, circa 1984-2002 (Box 114, Folder 47)
  - Homeless / City Hall Park, circa 1984-2002 (Box 114, Folder 48)
  - Brecht Sho[sp?} Sta[?], circa 1984-2002 (Box 114, Folder 49)
  - Steal It Bomber, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Art and Politics A and P, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - The Art Party, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Dancers Body, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Knows What Art Is, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Leonardo, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Country for Old Men, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Signed by the Artist, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Get the Gelt, 1985 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Can't Think of Anything Ta Draw, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Rev. Posters, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Art Against Apartheid, 1986 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Sucked Off, 1985 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Picasso, circa 1975-2002 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Lackey of Rich, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - Milano NYer Hotel, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Ted Berrigan, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - 2 Stools, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Small Presses, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - Art Fees, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 20)
  - Bull Blood, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 21)
  - Mysterious Longhair, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 22)
  - Artist Housing, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 23)
  - Esthetic Realism, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 24)
  - Kup, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 25)
  - Adversity, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 26)
  - Profound Cartoons, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 27)
  - Record Industry, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 28)
  - Mr. Christo, 1982 (Box 115, Folder 29)
  - Armando Shmuck, circa 1976-2002 (Box 115, Folder 30-31)
  - Village Voice Cartoons, 1987-1991 (Box 115, Folder 32)
  - Pole-Stir, circa 1982-2002 (Box 115, Folder 33)
  - Falkland, 1982-1984 (Box 115, Folder 34)
  - Brits Still Know How, 1982 (Box 115, Folder 35)
  - Englantina, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 36)
  - Crown Jewel of England, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 37)
  - Brit War Museum, 1985 (Box 115, Folder 38)
  - Britannia Park, 1985 (Box 115, Folder 39)
  - Eliz Grenada, 1985 (Box 115, Folder 40)
  - Gauguin, circa 1981-2002 (Box 115, Folder 41)
  - Buy Art, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 42)
  - I Didn't Know You Cd Type, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 43)
  - Originals, 1984, 1992 (Box 115, Folder 44)
  - Your Tax Dollars at Work, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 45)
  - 51 Single Sheet Version, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 46)
  - Did You Hold -- I Married a Shiksa, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 47)
  - America I Hate You, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 48)
  - No More Concert Hall For Me, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 49)
  - VV Carts Submits and Other Mags, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 50)
  - Smile, circa 1988-2002 (Box 115, Folder 51)
  - Brian, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 52)
  - Skywriter Original and Copy, circa 1984-2002 (Box 115, Folder 53)
  - Kissinger / Nose / Prick, 1994 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - City Park Disposess, 1964-1989 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Specials / Spots and C, circa 1989-2002 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Impeach the President, 1991 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - This Next Tune is Called, circa 1989-2002 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - High Rollers Military Bands, 1982-1983 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Assorted Tuli Kupferberg Cartoons, 1982-1985 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Many of These Cartoons Have Disappeared, circa 1984-2002 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Basic Choices, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Unsorted or To File, 1996-1997 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Load of Shit, circa 1984-2002 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Here Comes the Humane Society, 1990 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Genealogist, circa 1984-2002 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Garden Tool, circa 1995-2002 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Shit Pie, 1986 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - No Shopping Bag, 1997 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Catshit, 1996 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Oat Bran, 1990 (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Socrates, circa 1984-2002 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Roaches "Combat" and Disease, 1989 (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - Food Chain Expert, 1992 (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - Out of Order, circa 1984-2002 (Box 116, Folder 22)
  - Veally, circa 1991-2002 (Box 116, Folder 23)
  - Brave New War, circa 1984-2002 (Box 116, Folder 24)
  - Roaches, circa 1984-2002 (Box 116, Folder 25)
  - Chimps, circa 1984-2002 (Box 116, Folder 26)
  - Littering, 1987-1988 (Box 116, Folder 27)
  - Lemon -- Sperm, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 28)
  - Alone at Last, circa 1984-2002 (Box 116, Folder 29)
  - Apple Jacks, 1987 (Box 116, Folder 30)
  - Bull, 1981, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 31)
  - Lobsters, 1984 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Someday, Son, 1982 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - When Reds are Green, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Old Farts At Home -- Nose Hair Clipper, 1990 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Hamburger, circa 1984-2002 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Craziest Monkeys, 1990 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Icelandic Fish, 1989 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Greenpeace, 1989 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Old Farts At Home -- Grace, 1990 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Recycling -- Shit -- Stained Pants, 1990 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Brazil -- Demographics, 1990 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Pigs Ass and Avian Ova, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Millet, circa 1984-2002 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Granola Clusters, 1983 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Hominidae, 1985, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Asbestos, circa 1982-2002 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - More to Life than Roaches, circa 1984-2002 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - For: Craig Silver Alternative Media, circa 1984-2002 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Paper Sky, circa 1984-2002 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - A Kinder, Gentler Assault Rifle, 1989 (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Pres -- Elect Bush, 1989 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Noriega and Bush, 1989 (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - E. Pluribus Anum, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - Heroes, 1983-1984 (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - Reagan Bio, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 25)
  - Tickle Babies, circa 1984-2002 (Box 117, Folder 26)
  - Just a Sound Check, Folks, circa 1984-2002 (Box 117, Folder 27)
  - Liars Don't Kill, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 28)
  - Old People are Useless, 1984 (Box 117, Folder 29)
  - Founding Fathers / Fadders, 1985-1988 (Box 117, Folder 30)
  - Hot Air, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 31)
  - Not Yet Begun to Kill, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 32)
  - Contra Yup Tvoya Mat, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 33)
  - Shultz -- Weinberger, 1984 (Box 117, Folder 34)
  - Right Despots, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 35)
  - Great Moments in the History of America -- Renewed Military Draft, undated (Box 117, Folder 36)
  - Ad Agencies: Kiss My Ass for Free, 2005 (Box 117, Folder 37)
  - Einstein Never Wore Socks, 2002 (Box 117, Folder 38)
  - Nobody for President, 1984 (Box 117, Folder 39)
  - Media Shows Rev News, undated (Box 117, Folder 40)
  - The Tuli Show, undated (Box 117, Folder 41)
  - Ruined By Overeducation, undated (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - If at First You Don't Succeed, 2007 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - I Fucked Lincoln's Doctor's Cat, undated (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - I a Lady, undated (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Bennetts, James Gordon, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Harvard Share, 1995 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Border Headings, 1991 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Not the End of the World, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Possibles, 1997, 2001 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Newsboys, undated (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Great Moments in the History of the Media -- Jewboy Talk with Fucked Tongue, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Great Moments in Communication -- Poor Babies FBI and CIA, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - What's Sun -- X, undated (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Kronstadt, undated (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Teller, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Great Moments in the History of Justice, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Shootdown Friendly Fire Over Iraq, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - Shit, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - Time Out, 1995 (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - Food to the Poor, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - Shakespeare, undated (Box 118, Folder 22)
  - Fearless Fosdick, undated (Box 118, Folder 23)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Dickens American Notes, undated (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Satisfraction, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 25)
  - Anarchist Life, undated (Box 118, Folder 26)
  - Sin to Fuck a Priest?, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 27)
  - Non-Stop Action/Cancer, 1997 (Box 118, Folder 28)
  - Russian Robber Capital, 1997 (Box 118, Folder 29)
  - Kiss My Fat Ass, 1997 (Box 118, Folder 30)
  - Poor Health, 1997 (Box 118, Folder 31)
  - Fuck U, 1997 (Box 118, Folder 32)
  - Great Moments in the History of the Left -- Jeff -- Lenin, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 33)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Time Waits for Newsweek, undated (Box 118, Folder 34)
  - Your Son CD Gets Killed, undated (Box 118, Folder 35)
  - Always Get the Good Lines, undated (Box 118, Folder 36)
  - Beggars, undated (Box 118, Folder 37)
  - Wages, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 38)
  - Look Who's a Nothing, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 39)
  - Jews Can Kill Too, 1982-1987 (Box 118, Folder 40)
  - Great Moments in the History of the Media -- Van Gogh / Seminar, undated (Box 118, Folder 41)
  - Past Life Regression, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 42)
  - 5 Billion $ Secret, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 43)
  - Hudson -- Life, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 44)
  - Social Text, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 45)
  - CIA and Russia (Holzman) Song and NYT, 1991 (Box 118, Folder 46)
  - What Govt Is, undated (Box 118, Folder 47)
  - Read the Note! Read the Note!, 1995 (Box 118, Folder 48)
  - Sex Every Night, undated (Box 118, Folder 49)
  - Downsizing PR, undated (Box 118, Folder 50)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Mt. Sinai, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 51)
  - Pen Is, undated (Box 118, Folder 52)
  - Smart Bombs, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - S.A. Stampede, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Psycho Writer, 1995-1996 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Book of Perverbs -- One Man's Shit, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Great Moments in the History of the Media -- Nobody, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Great Moments in the History of Business -- Chem, 1994 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - NATL Sound, undated (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- British Journalist -- Wolfe, 1994 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Altria to Fool Ya, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Unsorted, 1995-1997 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Beauty is Truth, undated (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Is America a Fraud?, 2007 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - This Just In, circa 1984 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Sort, undated (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Unsorted 2, undated (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Unsorted 1, undated (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Marx on Capital -- On 3, 1994 (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - Submission Packet to The Village Voice, circa 1993 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Cartoons / Collages on Journalism and Art (Recent), undated (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous, 1982-1985 (Box 119, Folder 20)
  - Homo Erectus, undated (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - Slave Market, 2002 (Box 119, Folder 22)
  - Book of Perverbs -- Patrick Henry, 2007 (Box 119, Folder 23)
  - Our Arses and Stupidities, 2008 (Box 119, Folder 24)
  - Birds and Bees, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 25)
  - Lucky Jim, 1986-1998 (Box 119, Folder 26)
  - Burn People Not Flags, 1989 (Box 119, Folder 27)
  - Laika, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 28)
  - Space Rat, 1993, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 29)
  - Satellite, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 30)
  - Why Challenger Failed, 1986 (Box 119, Folder 31)
  - Miracles, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 32)
  - Sex, 1998-2000 (Box 119, Folder 33)
  - Sex -- Kid: Fig Leaf X-tra / Gun Naked, 1999 (Box 119, Folder 34)
  - Sex: Jou Jou Bust, 1999 (Box 119, Folder 35)
  - Sex -- Teach Yourself Fucking, circa 1997 (Box 119, Folder 36)
  - Sex -- Scholars All Agree, undated (Box 119, Folder 37)
  - Sex -- All You Ever Do Is Complain, 1989 (Box 119, Folder 38)
  - Sex -- Wrong About Massachusetts, undated (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Sex -- Form Follows Function, undated (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Sex -- War: Wanna Fuck, undated (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Sex -- Land of Mystery, undated (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Sex -- Hero Worship, undated (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Sex -- Yap-Yum, undated (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Sex -- Admiral Rape, undated (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Sex -- Cocksure, 1985 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Sex -- What's the Rush?, undated (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Sex -- Snakes, 1993 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Sex -- Eve and Adam Wear Clothes So Ashamed, 1995 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Sex -- Mom and Dad, 1989 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Sex -- Old Fucks at Home -- Group Marriage Aids, 1990 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Sex -- I Hate Dykes, 1992 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Sex -- Let Him Eat Cock, 1990 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Sex -- We Made Love, circa 1997 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Sex -- One Size Fits All, undated (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - Sex -- Read My Lips, 1992 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - Sex, circa 1980-1999 (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Sex -- 104, undated (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - Sex -- Old Fucks at Home -- Flirt Globally, undated (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - Sex -- Fart Feller, undated (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - Sex -- Beast with 2 Flacks, 1990 (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Sex -- Phallic Symbol, 1990 (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - Sex -- Nympho Maniac, 1993 (Box 120, Folder 25)
  - Sex -- Pussy Juice, undated (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Sex -- Old Fucks at Home -- Erotic Baker, 1990 (Box 120, Folder 27)
  - Sex -- Cynic Stuff, undated (Box 120, Folder 28)
  - Sex -- Safe Sex, undated (Box 120, Folder 29)
  - Sex -- AIDS OK, 1989 (Box 120, Folder 30)
  - Sex -- Sextras, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Sex -- The Chancellor, undated (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - Sex -- Slept With 100 Women, 1997 (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - Automatic Scientists, undated (Box 120, Folder 34)
  - Dog Raft It!, 1998 (Box 120, Folder 35)
  - Alone at Last, undated (Box 120, Folder 36)
  - If I Gave You My Money, undated (Box 120, Folder 37)
  - Sit Up Straight, undated (Box 120, Folder 38)
  - Great Moments in the History of Marxism, circa 1980-2008 (Box 120, Folder 39)
  - Shoemaker Between Iraq, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 40)
  - Nuclear Age Salute, 2001 (Box 120, Folder 41)
  - Assorted Tuli Kupferberg Cartoons, 2004-2005 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Mine is Proper, circa 1980-2008 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Asses in Midstream, circa 2004-2008 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Labor Daze Carts and CC, circa 1980-2005 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Give War a Chance, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Che NYer, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Kill Fraulein?, 1998 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Lefebre, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Great Moments in the History of the Monarchy -- Tina Brown / Di / Chuck, 1994 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Marcus Aurelius, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Rubaiyat / Fitzgerald / Myself When Young, 2007 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - You Can...Harvard Man / Old Farts at Home, 1990, 2007 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - A Song A Day, 2008 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - War If Everybody Came, 2008 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Kropotkin, 2008 (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Penis Mightier Than Sword, 2007 (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - Estrogen, circa 1980-2008 (Box 121, Folder 17)
  - Electric Cigarettes, 1998 (Box 121, Folder 18)
  - Anger is a Fool, 2008 (Box 121, Folder 19)
  - Flea Banana, 2008 (Box 121, Folder 20)
  - Whole World is Crazy, 2008 (Box 121, Folder 21)
  - Elections: Traps for Fools, 2008 (Box 121, Folder 22)
  - Shredder, 1994 (Box 121, Folder 23)
  - Marx at British Museum Xmas Eve, 2008 (Box 121, Folder 24)
  - The New Cabinet, circa 1980-2008 (Box 121, Folder 25)
  - Assorted Book of Perverbs and Miscellaneous, circa 1980-2008 (Box 121, Folder 26)
  - Crazy Journalists, 2007 (Box 121, Folder 27)
  - My Ol' President Lied Over the Ocean, 2008 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - There is a House in New York Town / They Call the "Stock Exchange", 2008 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Go to the Sluggard Thou Ant, 2008 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - First Thot, 2007 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Presidents Annex, circa 2006-2008 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Military Presidents, 2003-2004 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Tuli's Sent to Ed / Eds, circa 2007 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Broad: No War, 1998 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Giuliani Considers Running, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Shitle of Liberty Bomb, 1999 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Kids Directory, 1985 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Perfect Soldier, 2004 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Post-Primate, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Human Stupidity, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - What the Hell was That?, circa 1980-2008 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - Roasted Turkeys, 2000 (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - Euripedes, 1998 (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - Worst Book...Read, circa 1980-2008 (Box 122, Folder 18)
  - Congress of Gold, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Cartoons, 1995, 2004 (Box 122, Folder 20)
  - Tobacco Miscellany, circa 1980-2008 (Box 122, Folder 21)
  - Opium Wars, circa 1995 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Marine Xmas Toys for Tots, 1987 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Flow My Country Tis of Thee, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Welcome to Cancerville, circa 1980-2008 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Salute to Kool, 1985 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Looters, circa 1992-2008 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, circa 1980-2008 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Work / Source Material, 1983-1987 (Box 123, Folder 8-9)
  - Crawford and Tuli, 1982 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Prizes, 1997 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Child Labor, 1977-1994, undated (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Kosher Dog Food, 1995 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Fucking Animals!, undated (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - Incest, 1984 (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - Lennon -- Goldman, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - Pornography -- Adolescent Sexuality, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - Dick, circa 1980-2008 (Box 123, Folder 18)
  - Henry Miller was a Prick, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 19)
  - Washington Monuments, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 20)
  - Old Fucks at Home -- Blow on It, 1990 (Box 123, Folder 21)
  - It's All Been Said, circa 1980-2008 (Box 123, Folder 22)
  - Headache -- Thank God, circa 1980-2008 (Box 123, Folder 23)
  - Sex -- Wanna Fuck, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 24)
  - Get the Code Book, circa 1980-2008 (Box 123, Folder 25)
  - Want a Fuck?, circa 1980-2008 (Box 123, Folder 26)
  - Anti-Porn Activist, 1987 (Box 123, Folder 27)
  - Yank Pants, 1987 (Box 123, Folder 28)
  - Woman Discovers Man, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 29)
  - Food of Love, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 30)
  - Ladakh, circa 1980-2008 (Box 123, Folder 31)
  - Today -- 1872 cover, circa 1980-2008 (Box 123, Folder 32)
  - Hippies and C, undated (Box 123, Folder 33)
  - Do You Do Sex? Not Since 60's, circa 1980-2008 (Box 123, Folder 34)
  - Sage -- Koresh, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 35)
  - The 60's Coming Back, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Sri Garneesh Godchoy, circa 1980-2008 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- 60's are Over, 1994 (Box 124, Folder 3-4)
  - Berrigan Bros, 1984 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Beautiful Woman / Village Voice, 1984 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Sports / Single Mother, circa 1980-2008 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Sports -- Boxing, circa 1980-2008 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Sports -- Philosophy of Baseball, 1998 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Sports -- Mountain Idiots / Everest, 1992, 2001 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Sports -- Spartans Invent Football, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Sports -- Moral Equipment of War, circa 1980-2008 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Sports -- Wanna Thank Jesus, circa 1980-2008 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Sports -- Football, 1984 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Sports -- Good Training for Sport, circa 1980-2008 (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - Sports -- T-Shirt -- Village Voice, circa 1981 (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Sati, 1987 (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - Figment of Imagination, circa 1980-2008 (Box 124, Folder 18)
  - I Forgot to Have a Life, circa 1986-2008 (Box 124, Folder 19)
  - Fuck Snakes, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 20)
  - Fuck Ya! In Big Trouble, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 21)
  - God Proposes / Woman Disposes, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 22)
  - Incentive, 1983-1984 (Box 124, Folder 23)
  - Eat Fish, circa 1980-2008 (Box 124, Folder 24)